Printed Maps Printed.Maps
American Philosophical Society
- North America
  - United States Of America
    - Florida
      - Map of the territory of Florida. From its northern boundary to lat: 27B0, 30' N. connected with the delta of the Mississippi. Annexed to the report of the board of internal improvement... relating to the canal contemplated to connect the Atlantic with the Gulf of Mexico. U.S. Topographical E
        Insets: 15 surveys of sounds and bays; Gulf of Mexico with surrounding territory.
        Poussin sent Secretary John Vaughan a copy of the report "on the contemplated canal across the Peninsula of Florida" with a map. The map, he assured Vaughan, "was constructed with the greatest care and record [sic] all facts of actual survey" (Archives. Poussin to Vaughan; 11 June 1830. Transactions, n.s., vol. 4).
        Presented and autographed by William Tell Poussin, 11 June 1830.
      - Map of the seat of war in Florida, compiled by orders of Bvt. Brigr. Genl. Z. Taylor, principally from the surveys and reconnaissances of the officers of the United States Army. By Capt. John Mackay and Lieut. J. E. Blake. U.S. Bureau of Topographical Engineers. [Washington: 1839]., 1193; Scale: 2 cm. = 9 mi.; Size: 103.2 x 73.8 cm.; Colored.; John Mackay and J. E. Blake.; W. J. Stone.
      - The Bahama banks and gulf of Florida. By Edmund Blunt. New York: E. & G. W. Blunt: 1841., 1194; Size: 97.8 x 125.8 cm.; Edmund Blunt.; R. M. Gaw.
        Inset: Chart of Key West.
        The Blunts "spent a great deal of money in keeping up our charts to the latest surveys.... Our Chart, & our Coast pilot, contained a description of the shoal on which the Florida was short time since lost; & particular directions respecting the Coasts of New Jersey." The Blunts also wrote that their "new chart of the Bahama Bank" was the most dangerous section for American vessels and it differed from the British charts [Archives. E. Blunt to J. Vaughan, 16 October 1841].
        Presented and autographed by Edmund and G. W. Blunt, 16 October 1841.
      - Key West harbor and its approaches. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. From a trigonometrical survey under the direction of A. D. Bache. Hydrography by the party under the command of Lieut. John Rodgers. 1855. [Washington: 1855]., 1195; Scale: 1:50,000.; Size: 61.8 x 86.6 cm.; A. D. Bache, J. E. Hilgard, I. H. Adams, E. K. Knorr, and John Rodgers.; E. Yeager, E. F. Woodward, and H. M. Knight.
        Inset: Sub-sketch of Key West harbor.
        Presented by A. D. Bache, 6 March 1857; by the U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey through Spencer C. McCorkle, 14 December 1885.
      - St. John's River, Florida, from Jacksonville to Hibernia. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. 1884. [Washington]: 1884., 1196; Scale: 1:40,000.; Size: 81.5 x 53.1 cm.; A. Lindenkohl, H. G. Ogden, J. B. Baylor, and C. M. Chester.; R. F. Bartle, F. Courtenay, E. A. Maedel, and J. G. Thompson.
      - Coast chart no. 177. Tampa Bay, Florida. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. [Washington]: 1885., 1197; Scale: 1:80,000.; Size: 83.1 x 98.9 cm.; H. G. Ogden, W. I. Vinal, J. Hergesheimer, E. B. Thomas, H. B. Mansfield, J. M. Hawley, R. Platt, A. Braid, E. Smith, and C. M. Chester.
      - State of Florida. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources, under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1911. Washington: Eckert Litho. Co.: [1911]., 1198; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 102.7 x 81 cm.; Colored.; Eckert Lith. Co. and Wm. Bauman, Jr.; I. P. Berthrong.
        Inset: Western panhandle of Florida.
      - A new sectional map of Florida. U.S. Department of Agriculture. Buffalo, N.Y.: Wm. P. Northrup: 1913., 1199; Scale: 1 in. = 10 mi.; Size: 110.3 x 79.4 cm.; Colored.
        Inset: Panhandle of western Florida.
    - Alabama
      - Mobile bar. [1775]., 1200; Scale: 1 in. = ca. 2 mi.; Size: 9 x 15 cm.; B. Romans.
        At top of page is: "Page LXXXV of the Appendix."
        In: Bernard Romans, A concise natural history of East and West Florida; containing an account of the natural produce of all the southern part of British America in the three kingdoms of nature, particularly the animal and vegetable. New York: 1775.
        Wheat: 487
      - Map of Alabama constructed from the surveys in the General Land Office and other documents. By John Melish. Philadelphia: Melish: 1818 [29 October 1818]., 1201; Scale: 1 in. = 15 mi.; Size: 68.1 x 48.5 cm.; Colored.; John Melish.
      - Map of four townships granted to the French emigrants in Alabama. N.p.: [ca. 1830]., 1202; Size: 19.2 x 24.9 cm.
        Map shows Black Warrior or Tuskaloosa River.
      - Entrance to Mobile Bay. U.S. Coast Survey. From a trigonometrical survey under the direction of A. D. Bache. [Washington]: 1851., 1203; Scale: 1:40,000.; Size: 70.5 x 48.1 cm.; A. D. Bache, F. H. Gerdes, R. H. Fauntleroy, W. E. Greenwell, C. P. Patterson, and J. J. Ricketts.; R. T. Knight, S. T. Pettit, and W. Smith.
        Presented by A. D. Bache, 6 April 1852; received 21 May 1852.
      - Mobile Bay, Alabama. U.S. Coast Survey. From a trigonometrical survey under the direction of A. D. Bache. [Washington]: 1856., 1204; Scale: 1:80,000.; Size: 95.7 x 73 cm.; A. D. Bache, C. M. Eakin, F. H. Gerdes, W. E. Greenwell, B. F. Sands, J. Alden, C. P. Patterson, C. Mahon, and J. J. Ricketts.; S. Siebert, F. Dankworth, J. Knight, J. H. Goldthwaite, J. V. N. Throop, and H. M. Knight.
      - Mobile Bay, Alabama. From a trigonometrical survey under the direction of A. D. Bache, Superintendent of the Survey of the Coast of the United States. Triangulation by C. M. Eakin & F. H. Gerdes. Topography by W. E. Greenwell. Hydrography by the parties under the command of Lieuts. B. F. Sands, J. Alden & C. P. Patterson. Aids to navigation corrected to 1885. N.p.: 1885., 1205; Scale: 1:80,000.; Size: 96.5 x ca. 71 cm.; A. D. Bache, C. M. Eakin, F. H. Gerdes, W. E. Greenwell, B. F. Sands, J. Alden, and C. P. Patterson.; S. Siebert, E. Dankworth, J. Knight, and J. H. Goldthwait.
      - Maps of Muscle Shoals canal, Tennessee River, showing proposed intercoastal canal... U.S. War Department. Corps of Engineers. Made under the direction of Lt. Col. J. W. Barlow. Washington: Norris Peters Co.: [1890]., 1206; 4 maps.; Sizes: 13.9 x 39; 22.7 x 35.4; 30.5 x 45.5; and 29.8 x 268.6 cm.; Colored.; Julius Shutting, John H. Morgan, and J. W. Barlow.
      - Map of the state of Alabama. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of Harry King. 1895. New York: Julius Bien: [1895]., 1207; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 82.2 x 53.5 cm.; Colored.; Harry King, Daniel O'Hare, and Robert H. Morton.; Julius Bien.
      - State of Alabama. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from official records of the General Land Office, U.S. Geological Survey and other sources. Under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1915. [New York: 1915]., 1208; Scale: 1 in. = 12 statute mi.; Size: 81.7 x 53.4 cm.; Colored.; I. P. Berthrong, Daniel O'Hare, and George A. Daidy.
        Insets: Chattanooga and vicinity, showing the Chickamauga and Chattanooga National Park; Birmingham-Bessemer; Mobile; Shiloh and vicinity.
    - Mississippi
      - Cat and Ship Island harbors. U.S. Coast Survey. From a trigonometrical survey under the direction of A. D. Bache. New York: Sherman & Smith: 1850., 1209; Scale: 1:40,000.; Size: 42.6 x 85 cm.; A. D. Bache, F. H. Gerdes, J. E. Hilgard, W. E. Greenwell, C. P. Patterson, and Charles Mahon.; Sherman & Smith and J. Knight.
      - State of Mississippi. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under supervision of A. F. Dinsmore. 1890. [Washington: 1890]., 1210; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 82.9 x 52.9 cm.; Colored.; A. F. Dinsmore and Robert H. Morton.
      - State of Mississippi. U.S. Geological Survey. George Otis Smith, director. [Washington]: 1910-1911., 1211; Scale: 1:500,000.; Size: 111.8 x 67.6 cm.; G. O. Smith, R. B. Marshall, and A. F. Hassan.
      - Mississippi. Rand, McNally & Co's new Business Atlas map of Mississippi. Chicago: Rand, McNally: 1911., 1212; Scale: 1 in. = 13 statute mi.; Size: 67 x 47.8 cm.; Colored.
      - State of Mississippi. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from official records of the General Land Office, U.S. Geological Survey, and other sources; under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. Washington: Eckert Lithographing Co.: 1915., 1213; Scale: 1:760,320.; Size: 83.9 x 52.5 cm.; Colored.; A. F. Dinsmore and I. P. Berthrong.; Eckert Lithographing Co.
        Inset: Jackson.
      - Mississippi. U.S. Department of the Interior. Geological Survey. George Otis Smith, director. [Washington]: 1916., 1214; Scale: 1:1,000,000.; Size: 57.2 x 35 cm.; George Otis Smith, R. B. Marshall, and A. F. Hassan.
    - South Central United States
      - A map of Louisiana and Mexico. Carte de la Louisiane et du Mexique, dressée par P. Tardieu, fils ainé, gravée par P. A. F. Tardieu, père. Paris: P. A. F. Tardieu and C. Picquet: New York: Anthony Girard: 1820., 1215; Size: 106.5 x 79.4 cm.; Colored.; P. A. F. Tardieu and Richomme.; P. Tardieu.
    - Louisiana
      - Plan of New Orleans & its environs. New Orleans:, 1803.; 1216; Size: 70.8 x 48.5 cm.; Colored.; J. L. Boqueta de Woiseri.
        Insets: Esplanade or Place of Arms; Louisiana Purchase; map of New Orleans & larger environs.
        Only three copies of this map are known.
      - Carte générale du territoire d'Orléans comprenant aussi la Floride occidentale et une portion du territoire du Mississippi. Dressée d'après les observations les plus récentes par Bmi. Lafon. Nouvelle Orléans. 1806., 1217; Scale: 1 degree = 25 common leagues; Size of paper: 87.5 x 131 cm.; B. Lafon.
        Presented by Benjamin Lafon, 16 February 1816.
      - A map of the state of Louisiana, with part of the Mississippi territory, from actual survey. By Wm. Darby. Philadelphia: John Melish: 1816 [8 April 1816]., 1218; Scale: 1:10 English mi.; Size: 80.2 x 114 cm.; Colored.; Samuel Harrison.; William Darby.
        Presented by William Darby, 17 May 1816.
        See: William Darby, A geographical description of Louisiana. Philadelphia: Melish: 1816.
      - Plan of the city and environs of New Orleans. Taken from actual survey. By B. Lafon. N.p.: 1816., 1219; Size: 50.4 x 54.2 cm.; Colored.; B. Lafon.
      - Topographical map of New Orleans and its vicinity. Embracing a distance of twelve miles up, and eight and three quarter miles down the Mississippi River and part of Lake Pontchartrain representing all public improvements existing and projected, and important establishments, accompanied by a statistical table containing the most accurate illustrations prefaced by a splendid view of New Orleans, &. Compiled from actual surveys and the best authorities by Charles F. Zimpel. New Orleans: 1834 [4 September 1834]., 1220; Scale: 1 in. = 6 mi.; Size: 155.2 x 160.1 cm.; Charles F. Zimpel.
        Insets: Plan of the banks of the Mississippi and adjacent country, extending from Caraby's district to A. Ducros' plantation being a continuation of the above map, on a scale of 2⅜ inches to the mile; Lake Pontchartrain; portrait of New Orleans; plan of New Orleans; Defeat of the British Army on the 8 of January 1815. Important buildings are depicted across the top of the map.
        Presented by Cash, Esq., 21 October 1836.
      - A new map of Louisiana, with its canals, roads & distances from place to place along the stage & steam boat routes. Philadelphia: Thomas, Cowperthwait & Co.: 1850., 1221; Scale: 1 in. = 30 mi.; Size: 29.4 x 36.5 cm.; Colored.
        Inset: New Orleans.
      - Map of the state of Louisiana. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from the official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of Harry King. 1896. Baltimore: Friedenwald Co.: [1896]., 1222; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 76.3 x 72.5 cm.; Colored.; Harry King and Daniel O'Hare.
      - Southern Louisiana, showing waterways, etc. in the New Orleans, La., engineering district. U.S. War Department. Corps of Engineers. Compiled from U.S. Engineers, Coast and Geodetic, U.S. Geological, U.S. Land, Railroad surveys & other data. U.S. Survey Office, Detroit, Mich.: [1915]., 1223; Scale: 1 in. = 6 mi.; Size: 77.5 x 138.4 cm.; Colored.; A. H. Guillot, R. P. Howell, Jr., Lansing H. Beach, and Edward H. Schulz.
        Insets: United States; the world.
      - State of Louisiana. U.S. Department of the Interior. Compiled from official records of the General Land Office and other sources under the direction of I. P. Berthrong. 1916. Washington: Eckert Lithog. Co.: [1916]., 1224; Scale: 1 in. = 12 mi.; Size: 69.9 x 72.2 cm.; Colored.; Eckert Lithographing Co.; I. P. Berthrong, A. F. Dinsmore, and Wm. Bauman, Jr.
        Inset: City of New Orleans.
    - Texas
      - Map of the river Sabine from its mouth on the Gulf of Mexico in the sea to Logan's Ferry in lat. 31° 58' 24" north. Shewing the boundary between the United States and the Republic of Texas between said points, as marked and laid down by survey in 1840, under the direction of the commissioners appointed for that purpose under the first article of the convention signed at Washington, April 25, 1838. Surveyed in 1840. Washington: [1840]., 1225; Scale: 1 in. = 1 mi.; Size: 74.1 x 426.3 cm.; J. D. Graham, Thomas J. Lee, George G. Meade, P. J. Pillans, D. C. Wilber, and A. B. Gray.; P. Haas.
        Presented by James D. Graham, 28 August 1842.
        See note on map 1227 for Graham's comments on this map.
      - Map of the river Sabine from Logan's Ferry to 32nd. degree of north latitude. Shewing the boundary between the United States of America and the Republic of Texas between said points, as laid down by survey in 1841, under the direction of the joint commission appointed for that purpose under the 1st article of the convention signed at Washington, 25th. day of April 1838. [Washington: 1841]., 1226; Scale: 10½ in. = 2 mi.; Size: 47.2 x 67.1 cm.; A. B. Gray.
        See: U.S. Congress, A collection of maps, etc., published by order of Congress. Washington: 1843, No. 173.
      - Part of the boundary between the United States and Texas, from Sabine River, northward, to the 36th. mile mound. Drawn from the notes of survey and copied for the use of the commissioners, under the convention of the 25th. April 1838. By J. Edmd. Blake. U.S. Army Corps of Topographical Engineers. [Washington: 1841]., 1227; 3 maps.; Scale: 2 in. = 1 mi.; Size: ca. 69 x 53 cm.; J. Edmund Blake, T. R. Conway, A. B. Gray and James Kearney.
        A 2 from Sabine River, northward to the 36th mile mound.
        B 2 North of Sabine River from the 36th to the 72nd. mile mound.
        C 2 North of Sabine River from 72nd. mile mound to Red River.
        Graham wrote that he was forwarding some maps and charts illustrating the demarcation of that portion of the boundary between the United States and the Republic of Texas, included between the mouth of the river Sabine, and the point where the due north line from 32° of N. latitude on that river, intersects the Red River. Also a chart of the entrance of the river Sabine. These maps and charts are from actual surveys executed, as particularly stated on the respective sheets, in the years 1840, and 1841. There are in all, ten sheets. The river Sabine from its mouth, to Logan's Ferry, consists of five sheets which I have had mounted in one continuous map for more convenient reference. This part of the series is printed in colours so as to define the line of the boundary with great minuteness.
        The latitudes and longitudes of several points, and the dip and declination of the magnetic needle, as expressed on these five sheets, are from actual observations made by myself while attached to the Commission on the part of the United States for marking out the said boundary [Archives. J. D. Graham to A. D. Bache, 28 August 1842. Minutes. Proceedings, vol. 2, p. 214. Donation book].
        See also: map No. 1225.
        See: United States Congress, A collection of maps, etc. pub. by order of Congress. Washington: 1843, Nos. 174-176.
      - Sabine Pass and mouth of the river Sabine in the sea. Surveyed under the direction of Maj. J. D. Graham... by Lieut. T. J. Lee... and P. J. Pillans, Texan army, attached to the joint commission for marking the boundary between the United States and Texas. U.S. Topographical Engineers. 1840. [Washington: 1841]., 1228; Scale: 2 in. = 1 mi.; Size: 65.7 x 46.4 cm.; J. D. Graham, T. J. Lee, and P. J. Pillans.
        See:U.S. Congress, A collection of maps, etc., published by order of Congress. Washington: 1843, No. 177.
      - Map of Texas and the country adjacent: compiled in the Bureau of the Corps of Topographical Engineers. U.S. War Department. From the best authorities. For the State Department, under the direction of Colonel J. J. Abert. By W. H. Emory. 1844. [Washington]: 1844., 1229; Scale: 2.5 cm. = 100 mi.; Size: 35.9 x 55.7 cm.; J. J. Abert and W. H. Emory.
        Presented by Joseph R. Ingersoll, 20 June 1845.
      - Galveston entrance, Texas. U.S. Coast Survey. From a trigonometrical survey under the direction of A. D. Bache. [Washington]: 1853., 1230; Scale: 1:40,000.; Size: 34.5 x 43.5 cm.; A. D. Bache, R. H. Fauntleroy, J. S. Williams, J. M. Wampler, T. A. Craven, A. S. Baldwin, A. Fornaro, and A. Balbach.; H. C. Evans and S. E. Stull.
        Presented by A. D. Bache.
      - Preliminary chart of Galveston Bay, Texas. U.S. Coast Survey. A. D. Bache Supdt. [Washington]: 1884., 1231; Scale: 1:200,000.; Size: 48.7 x 42.5 cm.; A. D. Bache, R. H. Fauntleroy, R. D. Cutts, J. M. Wampler, T. A. Craven, E. J. De Haven, E. M. Hughes, J. M. Mansfield, and C. W. Howell.
      - Map of Texas and parts of adjoining territories. U.S. Geological Survey. Compiled by and under the direction of Robert T. Hill. [Washington]: 1900., 1232; Scale: 1 in. = 25 mi.; Size: 79.7 x 90.1 cm.; Colored.; Robert T. Hill, Henry Selden, and Willard D. Johnson.
      - Railroad and county map of Texas. 1903. Railroad Commission of Texas. St. Louis, Mo.: Woodward & Tiernan: 1903., 1233; Scale: 1 in. = 25 mi.; Size: 79.5 x 89.4 cm.; Colored.
      - Geological map of a portion of west Texas, showing parts of Brewster, Presidio, Jeff. Davis, and El Paso counties, and south of the Southern Pacific R.R. By Benjamin F. Hill and J. A. Udden. University of Texas Mineral Survey. 1904. Buffalo, N.Y.: Matthews-Northrup Works: 1904., 1234; Size: 40.5 x 128.2 cm.; Colored; C. P. Scrivener, Benjamin F. Hill, and J. A. Udden.
      - [Topographical survey of the Terlingua quadrangle, Texas, in cooperation with the University of Texas Mineral Survey]. William B. Phillips, Director. U.S. Geological Survey. Charles D. Walcott, Director. [Washington]: 1904. 3 maps. Editions of 1902 and 1904., 1235; Scale (2 maps): 1:125,000.; 1:50,000.; Size: 44.5 x 39 cm.; 16.6 x 48.5 cm.; Colored.; Charles D. Walcott, William B. Phillips, E. M. Douglas, Arthur Stiels, Fred McLaughlin, and J. E. Blackburn.; U.S. Geological Survey
    - Kentucky
      - This map of Kentucke, drawn from actual observations, is inscribed with the most profound respect, to the Honorable the Congress of the United States of America; and to his Excell[en]cy George Washington. By John Filson. Philadelphia: T. Rook: 1784. 3 facsimiles., 1236; Scale: 1 in. = 10 mi.; Sizes: 49 x 44.7 cm.; 48 x 44.6 cm.; 44.7 x 50 cm.; Henry D. Purcell.; John Filson.
        One facsimile was by the Kentucky Geological Survey, ser. VI, 1929. Source: Original in the private library of W.R. Jillson... Pub. date 20 December, 1929.
        Another facsimile is of the New-York Historical Society's copy of the map. Reprinted by the Kentucky Geological Survey, 15 January, 1931. Written on the scroll on facsimile is: "New York Historical Society from John Pintard. 1809."
        One facsimile presented by R.T. Durrett.
        There is also a reprint in Z.F. Smith's History of Kentucky. 1886.
        Wheat: 632
        See: John Filson, The discovery, settlement and present state of Kentucke.
      - Carte de Kentucke, d'après les observations actuelles: dediée a l'honorable Congrès des Etats-Unis de l'Amérique et à son excellence George Washington, commandant en chef des ses armées par leur très humble serviteur, John Filson. [Paris: Buisson: 1785]., [ca. 1785].; 1237; Scale: 3.5 cm. = 20 mi.; Size: 34.7 x 31.6 cm.; André.; John Filson.
        Removed from John Filson, Histoire de Kentucke... trad. par M. Parraud. Paris: Buisson: 1785.
      - A map of the state of Kentucky, drawn from the best authorities. 1793., 1238; Scale: 2.5 cm. = 42½ British statute mi.; Size: 15 x 19.1 cm.; T. Condor.
        In: Gilbert Imlay, A topographical description, following p. 400.
        Wheat: 640
      - Kentucky. [1795]., 1239; Scale: 2.5 cm. = ca. 57 mi.; Size: 15 x 18.5 cm.
        In: Joseph Scott, The United States gazetteer, opposite "Kentucky."
        Wheat: 643
      - Map of the state of Kentucky; with adjoining territories. New York: Smith, Reid and Wayland: 1795., 1240; Size: 37.4 x 44.3 cm.; A. Anderson.
        In: The American atlas. New York: J. Reid: 1796, no. 15.
        Wheat: 646
      - Kentuckey. [sic; 1796]., 1241; Scale: 2.5 cm. = ca. 57 mi.; Size: 14.7 x 19 cm.; W. Barker.
        In: Mathew Carey, Carey's American pocket atlas, following p. 98.
        Wheat: 644
      - Plan of Franklinville, in Mason County, Kentucky. [1796]., 1242; Scale: 2.5 cm. = 3,200 ft.; Size: 15.4 x 11.5 cm.; Tanner.
        In: William Winterbotham, An historical view of the United States, vol. 3, opposite p. 145.
        Wheat: 648
      - Plan of Lystra, in Nelson-County, Kentucky. [1796]., 1243; Scale: 2.5 cm. = ca. 800 ft.; Size: 16 x 11.5 cm.; Tanner.
        In: William Winterbotham, An historical view of the United States, vol. 3, opposite p. 144.
        Wheat: 649
      - The state of Kentucky and the adjoining territories from the best authorities. 1800., 1244; Size: 18.6 x 21.7 cm.; Scoles.
        In: John Payne, A new and complete system of universal geography, vol. 4, opposite p. 404.
      - A map of the state of Kentucky, from actual survey. Also part of Indiana and Illinois, compiled principally from returns in the Surveyor-General's office. By Luke Munsell. Frankfort: Luke Munsell: 1818 [16 December 1818]., 1245; Scale: 1 degree = 69.5 mi.; Size: 98.7 x 228 cm.; Colored.; H. Anderson.; Luke Munsell.
        There are two engraved scenes from pictures painted by Thomas Sully.
        Presented by Luke Munsell, 15 January 1819.
      - A new map of Kentucky, with its roads & distances from place to place along the stage & steam boat routes. [Philadelphia]: Thomas Cowperthwait: 1850., 1246; Scale: 1 in. = 30 mi.; Size: 29.6 x 35.5 cm.; Colored.
        Insets: Lexington & vicinity; Falls of the Ohio; Maysville and vicinity.
      - Map of eastern Kentucky, shewing the western outcrop of its coal field as determined by the surveys of 1858 and 1859, by Jos. Lesley, Jr., Philadelphia: J. Rehn: [1859]., 1247; Scale: 1 in. = 18 mi.; Size: 25 x 24.5 cm.; J. Rehn.; Joseph Lesley, D. Downes, and J. P. Lesley, Jr.
        Presented by George B. Wood, 6 January 1860.
      - Agricultural map of the Jackson Purchase. Geological Survey of Kentucky. John R. Proctor, Director. [New York?]: Julius Bien & Co.: 1886., 1248; Scale: 1:300,000.; Size: 33.6 x 51 cm.; Colored.; John R. Proctor, R. H. Loughridge, and J. B. Hoening.; Julius Bien & Co.